CHANGWEN LI

Melbourne, VIC 3000 ◆ 0473026835 ◆ arthurlicwofficial@gmail.com

Professional	SHMMARY
INOTESSIONAL	OUMINIANI

A student pursuing a Master of Computer Science at the University of Melbourne, anticipated to graduate in June 2024. Equipped with hands-on experience in full-stack development, mobile application development, and software testing. Demonstrates a deep understanding of object-oriented programming and a strong passion for optimizing software in terms of functionality and performance.

Profiles -

Personal Website:

https://www.changwenli.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/ArthurLCW

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/changwen-li/

SKILLS

- Language: English (IELTS 8, PTE 85), Chinese (native)
- Programming Languages: Python, C++, Java, MySQL, CSS, HTML5, JavaScript
- Technology stack: React, Node.js

- **Soft Skills**: Communication, Collaboration, Self-Learning
- Other Skills: Violin

EDUCATION

Master of Science: Computer Science, Expected in 06/2024

The University of Melbourne - Melbourne, VIC

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Science And Engineering, 06/2022 **The Chinese University of Hong Kong, Shenzhen** - Shenzhen, Guangdong

- Work Experience

Front-End Developer (Paid Intern), 12/2023 - 02/2024

Xiaomi – Beijing, China

- Collaborated with product managers, QA engineers, and back-end developers on the front-end development of several complex data management systems at Xiaomi. Notably contributed to a large-scale project, which involved over 7,000 exported modules and servicing more than 10,000 active users.
- Implemented advanced text replacement functionality within graphical representations to dynamically alter data labels under specific data conditions, enhancing user interaction.
- Developed a front-end feature that allows users to upload and manage sampling information, enhancing the usability of Xiaomi's product quality management system.

Cashier and Customer Service (Paid Part-Time), 11/2022 - 06/2023

Asuka Sushi – Docklands, VIC

• Communicated and understood customer needs.

• Managed customer payments through cash register.

Software Testing (Paid Intern), 06/2021 - 09/2021

Tencent Technology - Guangzhou, Guangdong, China

- Performed automated functional testing for enterprise WeChat with framework QT4C, developing over 200 automated test cases with 20,000 lines of code.
- Provided error feedback and analysis to improve product quality.
- Created TamperMonkey scripts to facilitate the download of error data from an automated testing platform, enhancing the efficiency of automated testing processes.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Personal Blog Website (www.changwenli.com):

- Developed a personal website to showcase personal information, publish blogs, and allow users to register and comment on blog posts.
- Hosted the website on AWS servers. Utilized React and Node.js.
- Implemented JWT for user account authentication.
- Integrated parallax scrolling and animation effects to bring the website to life with dynamic visual effects.
- Enhanced **web performance** through **lazy loading** of routes and images/videos, reducing the main page loading time by 57%.
- Source code: https://github.com/ArthurLCW/myWebsite

SOCIAL PRACTICE AND TEAMWORK

• Orchestra of CUHKSZ:

Part leader and part principal

• Model United Nations Association of CUHKSZ:

Academic director

• Young Sapling Volunteer Teaching Team:

Team leader

• Zhixing Social Research Team:

Team leader

AWARDS

- Bowen Scholarship 2018, academic award with \(\frac{1}{3}\) 3000 (around 6500 AUD)
- Bowen Scholarship 2019, academic award with \(\frac{1}{3}\) 3000 (around 6500 AUD)
- Bowen Scholarship 2020, academic award with ¥30000 (around 6500 AUD)
- Bowen Scholarship 2021, academic award with ¥30000 (around 6500 AUD)
- Melbourne Graduate Scholarship 2022, academic award with 5000 AUD